by H.
Thank you for watching
me
none
The second half of the bowling tournament, in which the winners of the preliminary rounds face off against each other.
Last time, the team that couldn't score any points due to handicap after a strike, and the team that couldn't score any points due to subtle pin action, the team that couldn't score any points, and the team that couldn't score any points due to subtle pin action, the team of Himura.
Before going bowling tonight
Tonight, before we go bowling, we're going to start with a halftime show by the eliminated members of the preliminary round.
And now for the second set of entertainment, Mr. Himura, I'm so looking forward to it, I know you love entertainment.
I'm glad they lost... because I'm a fan of Yamagata.
I want a dome show someday.
Let's go to the second round.
The first round...
Let's go.
The first round.
The first group of qualifiers.
Let's go.
Thank you.
What the hell?
Here we go.
It's out.
It's Kimuro!There it is, Kimuro.
What's this? He said a lot of things on the call.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Who was the first to call?
It started with Kimuro.
It didn't start with Kimuro.
I know, I know.
I want to eat, I want to lose weight, but I want to eat.
That's me.
I want to eat.
Science is science.
Science and science.
I see.
After yesterday's sawalong.
I'm about to start the chorus.
It's about to start the chorus.
I know, I know.
She's drunk.
Thank you.
It's funny.
I swear, while we were bowling, we were practicing like this.
How's Endo?
Mr. Hiduro's on his side.
Amazing.
It's crazy.
But it suits you.
It looks good on you.
Thank you very much.
That's great.
There's still one more pair to go.
Mr. Tenken came, and Nichiburo came.
They're totally tailored to us bananaman.
The lineup...
It's an all-star lineup!
I'm so excited!
I'm so looking forward to it.
And now for the entertainment for the three groups... these are the guests of honor.
Lillian! Lillian! Lillian!
Lillian, Lillian, Lillian!
Lillian, what is this?
It's not Lillian, it's Lillian!
I had no idea who they were at first.
At first, I thought it was...
That's Shibata, right?
I'm Shibata.
You're so cute.
Shibata's in TRF.
He's terrible.
Kaki looks like someone else.
Who is he?
One hour is not enough time for Mr. Sakazaki
Wow, Nogizaka Alfie is awesome!
You can do it, Alfie!
We came here to go bowling.
I don't get it. They came here to go bowling and they're doing this.
I don't get it.I don't get it.
I'd love to hear a few more songs at Alfie's.
It's amazing.
Lillian looks good on you.
It's Shibata.
I'm slowly saying it's Shibata.
Seriously, it's Shibata.
He's so cute!
After the fifth frame, the Hibla team is now leading by 3 points!
Next, the game frames again!
Karaoke rebase showdown!
Each team asked the two challengers to sing a Nogizaka song of their choice.
The ball is thrown only after the chorus!
The two teams will take turns bowling and relay karaoke songs.
Talking must be completed by the end of the chorus.
In this frame, the bowling scores are added up as they are.
The team with the lowest karaoke score
The team with the lowest karaoke score will have to wear cat ears while fighting from this point on.
The first team to attack was the Hiura team
Iwamoto and Kubo, a pair of 3rd term students, took on the challenge!
Are you okay with passing the microphone around?
That's our priority.
Can you handle the ball? Where?
I'm fine.
What's the matter, Uncle Dan? The day after tomorrow?
I didn't have it ready.
Got it!
Thank you for your help.
What's the difference between friendship and love?
He talked about it a lot when he was talking.
Afterwards.
When people ask me...
I don't know why you didn't notice
I'm sorry, you're sorry
Sorry, when you're the one everyone tells
Pro.
Ohhhhhh, Iwamoto's cover was so nervous that he blurted out the lyrics!
Kubo Kangan was concentrating on karaoke on the first pitch, but Iwamoto did a great job of recovering with an 8 pin!
I want to do this! It's super fun, why don't we do it live?
Next up were Tamar and Matsuo, the team's challengers, and they said that the first throw after the spare was the most important throw of the night.
Matsuo... the first throw is important... and that karaoke is important too... but the first throw has to be over 3 pins... so good luck with the bowling!
You can wear cat ears if you want.
Will the two of them be able to score as many points as Captain Shirara hopes?
Louder!
Good, good, good, good!
The two of them sang together, and without their voices freezing on the mike, they launched into the chorus of the song.
Here it comes! Here comes the chorus! Here comes the chorus! Singing!
First pitch is important!
Center! In the middle!
No one else can jump in.
Just me
Wish you'd grow up and mind your own business
Don't make me think you're in love
I knew it, you just got the first one
When the first one comes
The mannequin in uniform
The first throw was important! There you go!
The first pitch Matsuo, which Citara had emphasized so much, guttered and didn't win, and this frame ended up with 7 pins.
And with the karaoke lacking volume, the difference was too great, and the punishment for the cat ears went to the Sitara team.
Please familiarize yourself, Sitara!Mr. Sitara, please let me fit in.
I think he's having a good time, even if it's just for today.
But most of all, the first pitch by Matsuo really hurt.
So, if you do that in the future, I'll really close in on you where you can't see.
Next, Nimura's first pitch in the seventh frame was a strike that failed to catch the pet pin.
The strike failed to catch the pet pin.
Girl
Correct answer
Female
There are three pins!
I'd like to guess.
It's a father-son bowling tournament, isn't it?
Let's go to the creek.
Let's see if you can get the spare.
Second pitch, please.
The creek.
That's it... No, it's not the creek.
It's not Ogawa!
What was I thinking?
Oh no, I'm going to get sparked.
It's a spark!
Oh, no! Strike!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no!
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no! Who's there?
Who's there? - Mom!
Safe. Safe.
Honestly, please, get me a square.
I'll do my best
But Sugawara could only knock down one.
leaving the Kimura team in the lead.
The eighth frame is lost in the game again.
Not at all at all
FINGERLIGHT RALLY MORING
Go for it!
After spinning with the thrower wearing an eye mask
A game of bowling relying only on the voices of one's teammates
The first throw by the Himura team was by Iwamoto.
Can you throw it in the lane?
Then, let's start. Throw it, please.
Left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left, left.
Too far, too far, too far.
Back, back, back.
A little left, a little left. Back, back, back.
Don't go any further.
Don't go any further! Go back, go back, go back!
A little left. Go back. Go back.
That's how bad it is.
That's how shaky it is.
It's shaking, it's shaking, it's shaking.
Right, right.
Right.
It's only shaking here.
A little left, left, left, left.
Throw it.
Left, left, left, left.
Left-left-left! Go!Left, left, go!
Here we go. Here we go.
Good, good, good!
The whole team shouted as loud as they could against the obstruction.
But it's a little off... and it's a gawker!
Shut up!
We did our best, but...
Shut up, shut up, shut up, shut up!
Shut up!
Captain Himura makes the second throw!
Can he make up for Iwamoto's mistake?
Mr. Himura blindfolds himself and takes it all off.
Cover them all.
Not this and that!
I'll turn it.
No, I wanted to catch a cold.
I wanted to catch a cold.
Mr. Kanagawa, this mals your eyes.
Do you recognize my voice?
I can't hear you.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
To the left.
That's a totally different lane.
That's the wrong lane.
Wait a minute, I really can't hear you.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
It's off, it's off, it's off.
It's off, it's off, it's off, it's off.
Throw it, throw it.
I can't hear you.
Now, now.
It's off, it's off, it's off, it's off, it's off.
Wait a minute, let's go throw it.
You can throw it.
D-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d-d...
LOL!
Laughing.
Moment.
LOL!
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
I can't believe it.
I can't wait!
is
Kimura's team ended the play scoreless, as they were unable to get in front of it due to the lack of a threat.
And the first player on Shimoda's team, Tamura, also failed to light up!
Both teams struggled in this game.
Will they be able to catch the pin on the second throw?
It's really close!
Really, really close!
Oh, but...
Now, now, now!
Oh!
Oh, no, no, no, no.Oh, man. Oh, man.
Shidara's ball, fully focused on the ear, passed just past the gutter and hit the pin!
Finally, four points for the win!
I hear you've got a lot of luck... right, right, right...
You know what I'm talking about.
Remember those days...
Good, good, good... flow, flow, flow...
That's a big one!
Oh, no!
But Kubo couldn't keep up with Ogawa, the father-son bowler
regrettably, no spare!
Meanwhile, Sugawara's first throw to the Tadashi team was a guttershot, but Matsuo stubbornly beat him by 7 pins!
The team is now 2 pins ahead of the Himura team, and it's time for the penflay!
Bonus time!
What's this? It could be that team!
The 10 members who narrowly missed qualifying this time get to throw 10 balls at once, and get bonus points for each one they beat!
The Ice Village team chose 5 members from Gusu Lane, including the pusher, Yamagata, and the team below chose 5 members from Kisu Lane, including 2 members from Alfie's team.
What will be the outcome of the 10-man toss that could determine the winner?
Please! Please!
Oh, there it is! Wow!
OK!
You're one, right? It's 1, right?
What was the result?
First, let's start with the total score of the five members of Kimura's team!
21 points!
Oh, that's good! So-so!
That's a lot of points! So-so!
No, Mr. Mountain Sword, you're taking down a lot of pins! Oh, thank you, Yamaken!
Meanwhile, Lilia Takamizawa struck out, and the total score for Shimoda's team was
22 points!
That means 1.3!
What a close battle!
Thank you, everyone!
Thank you very much!
A game so good you'd think it was a fake, and the score difference was only 1 point!
And then, the final frame of the game, the final frame of the game, the final frame of the game!
Here we are in the final frame, and we're down by only one point after all this fighting.
This is the last point, but please, Mr. Himura, let's go!
Cosplay Bowling
In the final frame, both teams will be wearing cosplay costumes drawn by lot drawing.
The winners of the lottery are Sugawara and Iwamoto. What kind of handicap cosplay will they wear?
Please open the door.
Oh, it's hard to throw! That ume did it!
Oh, that one!
The robot soldier from Laputa and this is a banana.
If the banana is blocking my hand, I'm in trouble!
First up is the Himura team. Ogawa and Himura are transforming into robot soldiers.
Let's have them make an appearance.
Oh, Mr. Kimura, this is a little different.
Oh, I see.
Ogawa's hands are movable.
Mine doesn't.
Wow, this is not good.
This is not fair.
This is pretty bad.
I've got the microphone right here.I'm wearing my mike right here.
Okay, that's the last one for now. Let's go.
Oka, be careful.
It's hard to throw.
Sorry, sorry, sorry.
I can't throw.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no!
That was hard to throw!
No, but you're at a disadvantage.
Your hand has to be really bent.
Oh, no!
Last but not least, Mr. Himura.
Robot soldier, please.
Himura, the robot soldier who can't even use his arms.
What will happen to the winning throw?
Oh, but he's got a little bit of a shot.
Oh!
That's great!
Yeah!
Yes!
Nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah nah
Robot soldier meat warrior in the Nimura team's large format
The final frame is Nanuppy!
Against Shimoda's team
Hamada and Shimoda transform into banana cosplayers
Start
My face is stuck.
Not at all.
It doesn't matter.
This is totally fine.
I can afford it.
It doesn't matter.
Here you go.
Yes, sir.
Tamura, please.
Go for it!
Hang in there.
Oh, I did it!
We did it!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Tamura, who had been fighting so hard up to this point, turned in a two-kong turn at the critical moment.
If we're down by eight minutes, can the team make a last-ditch effort to take down more than nine pins?
I'm here.
Here we go. Last team, go ahead.
Last team, please.
Sam!
Yeah!
Yeah! What the hell is this?
Scarpiovers.
It's the last pair of pants.
So...
Kimura team 92Kimura Team 92
Shimoda Team 93
So, the pants team won!
What a great match!
Amazing now!
That's why
Reward!
Shall we open it?
What's that supposed to mean? The prize this time is the star both captains said they wanted. If it's a loppy cheese, the team gets it.
Kitagawa, it's your first time in the 4th season, right?
When you think back on the show... do you have any memories?
Only memories.
It was the show that made me realize how nice it is to be human.
"Nogizaka Kenkenchu" made me realize how nice it is to be human.
I started to like talking to people more and more.
That's why I thought
I thought it would be better if I could speak in a more interesting way.
I had a hard time with it.
But when I come here, I always have fun.
I'm glad it was fun.
It was a lot of fun, wasn't it?
I say funny things, and I say funny things.
I also participated in quiz shows outside the school.
It must have been hard for you to balance your studies and your idol career.
Well then, I guess this is my last message to the fans who have been watching the show.
Yes, thank you very much for everything.
I've worked really hard to make the show as enjoyable as possible for everyone who watches it.
I'm very happy to hear that you enjoyed the show.
It made me so happy.
Thank you very much.
I'm going to miss you.
I guess I suddenly felt it.
Good luck.
I'll do my best.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations on your graduation.
Good luck.
Class trophy, yay!
Yes!
That's great.
Oh, my God!
Trophies!
We're the winning team of the first class!
We did it!
The fact that there's a first round, that there's a trophy for this, that's...
Let's get to it.
Review
Good bye.
This is Yuri Kitagawa.
I'd like to guess what you all had for dinner last night.
Yes, yes, yes.
I see.
Wow, is everyone having omu-rice?
I'm amazed that you all have that much together. Please subscribe to our channel.